export const questionData = [
    {
        number: "1",
        question: "(2 + 2) x 2 = ?",
        options: ["4", "6", "8", "2"],
        answer: "8"
    }, 
    {
        number: "2",
        question: "Divide 20 by half and add 7",
        options: ["3", "47", "13", "17"],
        answer: "47"
    },
    {
        number: "3",
        question: "Which number do we get if we round the PI to the neares integer?",
        options: ["2", "4", "1", "5"],
        answer: "3"
    },
    {
        number: "4",
        question: "Double of half of 2",
        options: ["1/2", "4", "1<sup>2</sup>", "2<sup>2</sup>"],
        answer: "2"
    },
    {
        number: "5",
        question: "1 = 4 <br>2 = 8 <br>3 = 12 <br>4 = ?",
        options: ["14", "16", "20", "8"],
        answer: "1"
    },
    {
        number: "6",
        question: "A pen and a book cost 110 dollars. <br>The book cost 100 dollars more than pen. <br>How much dose it cost the pen?",
        options: ["100", "10", "5", "unknown"],
        answer: "5"
    },
    {
        number: "7",
        question: "Click on True",
        options: ["(a + b)<sup>2</sup> = a<sup>2</sup> + 2ab + b<sup>2</sup>", "3<sup>3</sup> = 27", "54 รท 3 = 18", "14 x 5 = 70"],
        answer: "True"
    },
    {
        number: "8",
        question: "You are running in a race with your friends and you just passed the 2nd place. <br>In which position are you?",
        options: ["1st", "3rd", "last", "unknown"],
        answer: "2nd"
    },
    {
        number: "9",
        question: "Which is the number of this question?",
        options: ["7", "10", "8", "9"],
        answer: "9"
    },
    {
        number: "10",
        question: "How many natural satellite dose Venus has?",
        options: ["0", "8", "9", "1"],
        answer: "0"
    },
    {
        number: "11",
        question: "Which was the answer of the second question?",
        options: ["3", "47", "13", "17"],
        answer: "47"
    },
    {
        number: "12",
        question: "Mirror image of an analogue clock shows the time as 2:30, What time is it?",
        options: ["9:30", "4:00", "2:30", "10:00"],
        answer: "9:30"
    },
    {
        number: "13",
        question: "Which question was skipped?",
        options: ["7", "8", "2", "11"],
        answer: "8"
    },
    {
        number: "14",
        question: "What result will you get, when all the nubers on telephone dial-pad are multiplied?",
        options: ["0", "45", "55", "362880"],
        answer: "0"
    },
    {
        number: "15",
        question: "What mathematical symbol can be put between 5 and 9, to get a value bigger than 5 and smaller than 9?",
        options: ["+", "-", ".", "+"],
        answer: "."
    },
    {
        number: "16",
        question: "Which is the biggest planet in our solar system?",
        options: ["Neptun", "Saturn", "Sun", "Jupiter"],
        answer: "Jupiter"
    },
    {
        number: "17",
        question: "Which question had no number?",
        options: ["14", "12", "9", "11"],
        answer: "12"
    },
    {
        number: "18",
        question: "In a pool lies a flower, the flower doubles in size every day, in 30 day it will cover the pool compeletly, in how many days will the flower cover half of the pool?",
        options: ["2", "15", "29", "16"],
        answer: "29"
    },
    {
        number: "16",
        question: "2x + y = 10, x - y = y, 2z = y + 6, z = ?",
        options: ["5", "3", "0", "2"],
        answer: "x"
    },
    {
        number: "17",
        question: "Save the man",
        options: ["", "", "", ""],
        answer: "20 click / timer"
    },
    {
        number: "18",
        question: "How do you enter a door?",
        options: ["", "", "", ""],
        answer: "knock knock dbl-click"
    },
    {
        number: "19",
        question: "Try your Luck!",
        options: ["", "", "", ""],
        answer: ""
    },
    {
        number: "20",
        question: "Only one chance",
        options: ["Click", "Don't Click"],
        answer: "Click"
    }
];